<resources>

    <!-- Launcher app name -->
    <string name="app_name">Tap, Tap</string>

    <!-- Generic -->
    <string name="search">Szukaj</string>
    <string name="close">Zamknij</string>
    
    <!-- Setup > Landing -->
    <string name="landing_title">Witaj w Tap, Tap</string>
    <string name="landing_button_get_started">Zaczynajmy</string>
    <string name="landing_button_skip_setup">Pomiń Konfigurację</string>

            <!-- Setup > Info -->
    <string name="setup_foss_info_title">Tap, Tap jest darmowy i otwartoźródłowy</string>
    <string name="setup_foss_info_content"><![CDATA[Tap, Tap is and always will be free, building off open source components. The source code is available for anyone to view and make edits to at the <a href=\"https://kieronquinn.co.uk/redirect/TapTap/github\">GitHub repository</a>. Official free downloads for the app are <b>only</b> available at <a href="https://kieronquinn.co.uk/redirect/TapTap/xda">XDA</a>, the <a href="https://kieronquinn.co.uk/redirect/TapTap/github">GitHub repository</a>, and <a href="https://kieronquinn.co.uk/redirect/TapTap/apkmirror">APKMirror</a>. The official app will always automatically offer to download updates from GitHub, if you have allowed internet access.]]></string>
    <string name="setup_foss_info_warning">Only install Tap, Tap from one of the official sources linked above. <b>If you downloaded from any other source, it is highly recommended you uninstall it and reinstall from one of the links above</b>. Tap for more info.</string>
    <string name="setup_foss_info_bs_title">Uwaga</string>
    <string name="setup_foss_info_bs_content">Tap, Tap używa Usługi Dostęponości. This gives it access to perform actions on your device automatically, and should not be granted to apps you do not trust. This is why Tap, Tap is open source - so you and everyone else who wants to can look at the code and verify it\'s not doing anything it shouldn\'t be.\n\nHowever, this guarantee  does not apply if you downloaded the APK from a source other than the official locations. If you downloaded from anywhere other than the GitHub repository, XDA or APKMirror, it is highly recommended that you uninstall it immediately and reinstall it from one of the official locations.</string>
    <string name="setup_foss_info_content_lower">Jeżeli podoba Ci się Tap, Tap i chcesz wspomóc autora finansowo, użyj linku znajdującego się w dolnej sekcji strony \"More\" po ukończeniu konfiguracji. Niezależnie czy dokonasz wpłaty, czy nie, Twoje wsparcie poprzez korzystanie z aplikacji będzie bardzo cenne. Dziękuję!</string>
    <string name="setup_info_next">Dalej</string>

    <!-- Setup > Notifications -->
    <string name="setup_notifications_title">Powiadomienia</string>
    <string name="setup_notifications_content">Tap, Tap używa powiadomień, aby informować Cię o wymaganiach dotyczących akcji oraz zastosowanych ograniczeń, a także o możliwych błedach i innych ważnych funkcjach aplikacji.\n\nProszę włącz powiadomienia, aby aplikacja mogła działać poprawnie. Możesz wyłączyć powiadomienie o działaniu aplikacji w tle</string>
    <string name="setup_notifications_request">Nadaj Uprawnienia</string>

    <!-- Setup > Gesture -->
    <string name="setup_gesture_toolbar">Konfiguracja Gestów</string>
    <string name="setup_gesture_device_size"><![CDATA[Wybierz najlepszy rozmiar odpowiadający Twojemu urządzeniu.<br><b>Aktualnie wybrany: %1$s</b><br>Jeżeli masz problem z rozpoznaniem akcji gestów, spróbuj innych modeli telefonów.]]></string>
    <string name="setup_gesture_loading">Ładowanie…</string>
    <string name="setup_gesture_info_hint">Stuknij dwukrotnie w tył telefonu, aby aktywować gest.\n<b>Spróbuj stuknąć mocniej używając czubka swojego palca wskazującego.</b></string>
    <string name="setup_gesture_info_help">Nie działa? Spróbuj zmienić rozmiar urządzenia i czułość w ustawieniach Konfiguracji Gestów</string>
    <string name="setup_gesture_info_success"><b>Wspaniale! Stuknij aby kontynuować.</b>\nTip: Jeżeli masz problem z użyciem gestów, możesz dostosować zakres i czułość w panelu Konfiguracji Gestów, lub później w ustawieniach.</string>

    <!-- Setup > Complete -->
    <string name="setup_complete_card">Akcje i Bramy mogą wymagać przyznania pewnych uprawnień podczas ich pierwszego dodania lub wykonania. Zwróć uwagę na pojawiające się powiadomienia, które pozwolą Ci ustawić wymagane uprawnienia.</string>
    <string name="setup_complete_title">Konfiguracja zakończona</string>

    <!-- Internet Permission Prompt -->
    <string name="dialog_internet_permission_text">Zezwól na dostęp do internetu?</string>
    <string name="dialog_internet_permission_desc">Aplikacja będzie używała internetu, aby pobierać specyfikacje urządzeń oraz sprawdzać dostępność aktualizacji.</string>
    <string name="dialog_internet_permission_allow_always">Zawsze zezwalaj</string>
    <string name="dialog_internet_permission_allow_open">Zezwól, gdy Tap, Tap jest włączony</string>
    <string name="dialog_internet_permission_deny">Odmów</string>

    <!-- Upgrade modal -->
    <string name="setup_upgrade_loading">Aktualizowanie ustawień…</string>

    <!-- No Gyroscope Modal -->
    <string name="modal_no_gyroscope_title">Niekompatybilne urządzenie</string>
    <string name="modal_no_gyroscope_content">Twoje urządzenie nie posiada wymaganego czujnika (żyroskop), niezbędnego dla tej aplikacji. Tap, Tap nie będzie działać na tym urządzeniu.</string>

    <!-- Disable Columbus Modal -->
    <string name="modal_disable_columbus_title">Wyłącz lub skonfiguruj Quick Tap</string>
    <string name="modal_disable_columbus_content"><![CDATA[System Quick Tap jest włączony na Twoim urządzeniu, ale nie jest poprawnie skonfigurowany. Proszę wyłącz lub skonfiguruj go poprawnie, inaczej Tap, Tap nie będzie działał poprawnie.<br>Quick Tap można znaleźć w ustawieniach System > Gesty.<br><br><b>Jeżeli próbujesz włączyć Native Mode, upewnij się że ustawiona jest akcja uruchomienia aplikacji Tap, Tap, oraz że nadałeś uprawnienia READ_LOGS. <a href="https://kieronquinn.co.uk/redirect/TapTap/nativesetup">Kliknij tutaj po więcej informacji</a>.</b>]]></string>
    <string name="modal_disable_columbus_card">Po wyłączeniu opcji systemowej Quick Tap musisz zrestartować urządzenie, aby niektóre funkcje Tap, Tap działały prawidłowo.</string>
    <string name="modal_disable_columbus_button">Otwórz Ustawienia</string>

    <!-- Settings UI -->
    <string name="settings_main_enable_tap_tap">Włącz Tap, Tap</string>
    <string name="setting_bottom_nav_settings">Ustawienia</string>
    <string name="setting_bottom_nav_gesture">Gesty</string>
    <string name="setting_bottom_nav_more">Więcej</string>
    <string name="menu_setup_wizard">Ponowna Konfiguracja</string>

    <!-- Settings > Gesture -->
    <string name="settings_main_battery"><b>Wyłącz optymalizację baterii</b>\nAby uniemożliwić zamykanie Tap, Tap przez system Android, gdy działa ona w tle, wyłącz optymalizację baterii</string>
    <string name="setting_actions_double">Akcje podwójnego stuknięcia</string>
    <string name="setting_actions_triple">Akcje potrójnego stuknięcia</string>
    <string name="settings_actions_desc_double">Ustaw akcje do wykonania, po dwukrotnym stuknięciu w tył swojego urządzenia</string>
    <string name="settings_actions_desc_triple">Ustaw akcje do wykonania, po trzykrotnym stuknięciu w tył swojego urządzenia</string>
    <string name="setting_gates">Bramy</string>
    <string name="setting_gates_desc">Ustaw sytuacje, w których gest nie powinien uruchamiać akcji</string>
    <string name="setting_feedback">Reakcje</string>
    <string name="setting_feedback_desc">Ustaw sposób, w jaki urządzenie powiadamia Cię o wykonaniu gestu</string>
    <string name="setting_feedback_vibrate">Wibracja</string>
    <string name="setting_feedback_vibrate_desc">Wibruj raz, gdy gest jest używany i akcja jest wykonywana</string>
    <string name="setting_feedback_wake">Wybudź urządzenie</string>
    <string name="setting_feedback_wake_desc">Włącz ekran urządzenia, jeśli jest wyłączony</string>
    <string name="slider_sensitivity_very_low">Bardzo słaba</string>
    <string name="slider_sensitivity_low">Słaba</string>
    <string name="slider_sensitivity_medium">Średnia</string>
    <string name="slider_sensitivity_high">Mocna</string>
    <string name="slider_sensitivity_very_high">Bardzo mocna</string>
    <string name="setting_feedback_override_dnd">Wibruj, mimo trybu Nie Przeszkadzać</string>
    <string name="setting_feedback_override_dnd_desc">Ignoruje tryb Nie Przeszkadzać i zawsze wibruje podczas wykonywania akcji</string>

            <!-- Settings > Gesture -> Action -->
    <string name="fab_add_action">Add Action</string>
    <string name="fab_remove_action">Remove</string>
    <string name="help_action">Actions are tasks that are run when you tap the back of your device twice. Actions are run in the order of the list - top to bottom, and only if requirements are met.\nTap for more info.</string>
    <string name="bs_help_action">Actions are tasks that are run when you tap the back of your device twice. Actions are run in the order of the list - top to bottom. If an action is able to run successfully, no further actions will be run. However, if an action is unavailable (eg. if the assistant for a "Launch assistant" action is already running, or if the requirements are not met), the next action below it will be run, and so on until one is run successfully.</string>
    <string name="bs_help_action_title">What are Actions?</string>
    <string name="item_action_when_empty">Add requirement…</string>
    <string name="item_action_when_not_empty_single">%1d requirement</string>
    <string name="item_action_when_not_empty_other">%1d requirements</string>
    <string name="item_action_app_uninstalled">Unknown app (%1s)</string>
    <string name="switch_triple">Enable Triple Tap</string>
    <string name="settings_actions_loading_actions">Loading Actions…</string>
    <string name="help_action_triple"><b>Note:</b> When triple tap is enabled, the double tap action may be slower to respond. This is due to the fact that it has to wait to see if a third tap will be performed before running the action.</string>
    <string name="settings_actions_triple_empty">No Triple Tap Actions set, tap Add Action to add one.</string>
    <string name="settings_actions_double_empty">No Double Tap Actions set, tap Add Action to add one.</string>

            <!-- Settings > Gesture > Action > Requirements -->
    <string name="action_when_gate_inverted">%1s (Inverted)</string>
    <string name="settings_when_gates_title">Requirements</string>
    <string name="settings_actions_when_gates_empty">No Requirements set, tap Add Requirement to add one.</string>
    <string name="settings_actions_loading_when_gates">Loading Requirements…</string>
    <string name="fab_add_requirement">Add Requirement</string>

            <!-- Settings > Gesture > Action > Add -->
    <string name="add_action_category_launch">Launch</string>
    <string name="add_action_category_launch_desc">Launch an app, shortcut or app shortcut</string>
    <string name="add_action_category_utilities">Utilities</string>
    <string name="add_action_category_utilities_desc">Take a screenshot, toggle the flashlight, open the app drawer or accept/reject a call</string>
    <string name="add_action_category_button">Buttons</string>
    <string name="add_action_category_button_desc">Simulate button presses, such as home, back, recents or power</string>
    <string name="add_action_category_sound">Sound</string>
    <string name="add_action_category_sound_desc">Control music, change the volume or control alarms</string>
    <string name="add_action_category_gesture">Gestures</string>
    <string name="add_action_category_gesture_desc">Simulate swipe actions in up, down left or right directions</string>
    <string name="add_action_category_accessibility">Accessibility</string>
    <string name="add_action_category_accessibility_desc">Accessibility specific actions, such as Google Voice Access and showing the Accessibility Button Chooser</string>
    <string name="add_action_category_advanced">Advanced</string>
    <string name="add_action_category_advanced_desc">Trigger Tasker tasks and events</string>
    <string name="settings_actions_add_category_selector_loading">Loading Actions…</string>
    <string name="settings_actions_add_action_selector_loading">Loading Actions…</string>
    <string name="settings_actions_add_category_selector_empty">No Actions Found</string>

    <!-- Action Chips -->
    <string name="action_chip_shizuku">Shizuku</string>
    <string name="action_chip_shizuku_desc">Wymaga aplikacji Shizuku lub sui</string>
    <string name="action_chip_root">Root</string>
    <string name="action_chip_root_desc">Wymaga dostępu root</string>
    <string name="action_chip_accessibility">Usługa</string>
    <string name="action_chip_accessibility_desc">Wymaga włączenia Usługi Ułatwień Dostępu</string>
    <string name="action_chip_gesture_accessibility">Gest</string>
    <string name="action_chip_gesture_accessibility_desc">Wymaga włączenia Usługi Ułatwień Dostępu Gestów</string>
    <string name="action_chip_tasker">Tasker</string>
    <string name="action_chip_tasker_desc">Wymaga aplikacji Tasker</string>
    <string name="action_chip_snapchat">Snapchat</string>
    <string name="action_chip_snapchat_desc">Wymaga aplikacji Snapchat</string>

            <!-- Settings > Gesture > Gates -->
    <string name="fab_add_gate">Dodaj Bramę</string>
    <string name="help_gate">Bramy to sytuacje, które mogą zablokować Gates are situations that can block the gesture from running any actions. In order for any action to be run, all the enabled gates must be open.\nTap for more info.</string>
    <string name="bs_help_gate">Gates are situations that can block the gesture from running any actions. In order for any action to be run, all the enabled gates must be open.\nIf a scenario is currently met, for example if the screen is off and the "Display off" gate is enabled, no actions will be run. You can add as many gates as you like, and enable/disable them using the toggles (rather than having to delete and re-add) to make configuration quicker and easier.</string>
    <string name="bs_help_gate_title">What are Gates?</string>
    <string name="settings_gates_loading_gates">Loading Gates…</string>
    <string name="settings_gates_header_native_mode"><b>Native Mode Enabled</b>\nWith Native Mode enabled, Tap, Tap will <b>never</b> work with the display off, regardless of which gates you select.</string>

            <!-- Settings > Gesture > Gates > Add -->
    <string name="add_gate_category_device">Device</string>
    <string name="add_gate_category_device_desc">React to device changes such as screen, charging and USB states</string>
    <string name="add_gate_category_sensors">Sensors</string>
    <string name="add_gate_category_sensors_desc">React to sensor data, such as when the device is in your pocket, or flat on a table</string>
    <string name="add_gate_category_audio">Audio</string>
    <string name="add_gate_category_audio_desc">React to audio-related events, such as being on call or playing music</string>
    <string name="add_gate_category_events">Apps</string>
    <string name="add_gate_category_events_desc">React to apps being open, including the keyboard and camera</string>
    <string name="gate_selector_unavailable">Sorry, this gate is not compatible with your device (%1s).</string>
    <string name="settings_gates_add_category_selector_loading">Loading Gates…</string>
    <string name="settings_gates_add_gate_selector_loading">Loading Gates…</string>
    <string name="settings_gates_add_category_selector_empty">No Gates Found</string>
    <string name="settings_gates_empty">No Gates set, tap Add Gate to add one.</string>

            <!-- Settings > Settings -->
    <string name="setting_gesture_model">Rozmiar urządzenia</string>
    <string name="setting_gesture_model_desc">Dostosuj rozmiar urządzenia podczas wyboru gestów.</string>
    <string name="setting_gesture_model_desc_not_available">Ta opcja nie jest dostępna, gdy Low Power Mode jest włączone.</string>
    <string name="setting_gesture_model_desc_not_available_native">Ta opcja nie jest dostępna, gdy Native Mode jest włączone.</string>
    <string name="setting_low_power_mode">Low Power Mode</string>
    <string name="setting_low_power_mode_desc">Run the gesture detection on the low-power Context Hub, rather than using the regular CPU to save battery</string>
    <string name="setting_low_power_mode_desc_unavailable">Low Power Mode is not available while Native Mode is enabled.</string>
    <string name="setting_gesture_sensitivity">Czułość</string>
    <string name="setting_gesture_sensitivity_desc">Change the sensitivity of the gesture by adjusting how much force is filtered out as \'noise\'. A lower sensitivity means the gesture will be harder to do on most devices, whereas a higher sensitivity is more prone to false detection.</string>
    <string name="setting_gesture_sensitivity_desc_disabled">A custom sensitivity value is set in the Advanced Settings, reset it to use this option.</string>
    <string name="setting_gesture_sensitivity_chre">Zmniejsz czułość</string>
    <string name="setting_gesture_sensitivity_chre_desc">Zmniejsz czułość gestów Tap, Tap, aby uczynić je trudniejszymi do wykonania.</string>

            <!-- Settings > Settings > Low Power Mode -->
    <string name="settings_low_power_mode_enable">Enable Low Power Mode</string>
    <string name="setting_low_power_mode_content">Low Power Mode uses the device\'s \"Context Hub\", which allows for running \"nanoapps\" on the low-power CPU. For this to work, there must be the Columbus nanoapp compiled for your device installed, which has to be done by the OEM. Tap, Tap is then able to use this app, in the same way that the system Quick Tap feature does, to detect the gesture in a significantly more power efficient way.\n\n<b>Shizuku (or alternatively sui) is also required for this option, as it requires system permissions not available to user apps.\nOn Android 13 or above, Sui is required due to platform changes beyond Tap, Tap\'s control.</b>\n\n<b>Note: You may need to reboot after enabling this option for the first time for it to take effect.</b></string>
    <string name="settings_low_power_mode_error_shizuku">Shizuku or sui is required for this option to work. Shizuku will work without root, but if your device is rooted, it will be able to start automatically on boot. If you are using the <b>sui</b> Magisk module, tap below to request permission.</string>
    <string name="settings_low_power_mode_error_button_shizuku">What\'s Shizuku / Sui?</string>
    <string name="settings_low_power_mode_error_button_sui">Request <b>sui</b> permission</string>
    <string name="settings_low_power_mode_error_not_compatible">Sorry, this option is not compatible with your device\n<b>Note:</b> If you are running Android 13 or above, you <b>must</b> be rooted and use Sui to use this option, Shizuku is no longer acceptable due to platform changes outside of Tap, Tap\'s control.</string>
    <string name="settings_low_power_mode_error_toast">Shizuku is not running, start it to enable Low Power Mode</string>

            <!-- Settings > Settings > Native Mode -->
    <string name="settings_native_mode">Native Mode</string>
    <string name="settings_native_mode_desc">Native Mode uses the system Quick Tap feature to run with low battery usage, using Shizuku or Sui, with some restrictions.</string>
    <string name="settings_native_mode_desc_unavailable">Native Mode is unavailable when Low Power Mode is enabled.</string>
    <string name="settings_native_mode_enable">Enable Native Mode</string>
    <string name="settings_native_mode_launch_toast">Enable Quick Tap in System > Gestures &amp; set Tap, Tap as the Open app Action</string>
    <string name="settings_native_mode_launch_toast_disable">Disable Quick Tap in System > Gestures</string>
    <string name="setting_native_mode_content">Native Mode uses the built-in Quick Tap feature on Pixels to run Tap, Tap. This has the benefit of having almost as low battery consumption as Low Power Mode, but does have two downsides:\n• <b>Tap, Tap will not work when the screen is off</b>\n• <b>Triple Tap may be less reliable</b>\n\nTo enable Native Mode, you must enable Quick Tap in the system settings, and set the action to launch Tap, Tap.</string>

            <!-- Settings > Settings > Model Picker -->
    <string name="settings_model_picker_loading">Ładowanie…</string>
    <string name="settings_model_picker_tab_newest">Najnowsze</string>
    <string name="settings_model_picker_tab_legacy">Stare</string>
    <string name="settings_model_picker_tab_oem">OEM</string>
    <string name="settings_model_picker_device_size">Wysokość: %1smm (%1sin)</string>
    <string name="settings_model_picker_recommended">%1s (Rekomendowane)</string>
    <string name="settings_model_picker_header_newest">Newest models are from Android 12 and are more accurate than the legacy models.\n\n<b>Note:</b> Sometimes the closest size is not the best for your device, you may need to try all the sizes to find the one that is best for you.</string>
    <string name="settings_model_picker_header_legacy">Legacy models are from Android 11 and are less accurate than the newer models.\n\n<b>Note:</b> Sometimes the closest size is not the best for your device, you may need to try all the sizes to find the one that is best for you.</string>
    <string name="settings_model_picker_header_oem">OEM models are from device manufacturer implementations of Quick Tap\n\n<b>Note:</b> There are no size recommendations for these models</string>

    <!-- New (Android 12) models -->
    <string name="tap_model_redfin_name">144.7mm [5.7in] (Mały)</string>
    <string name="tap_model_redfin_desc">Utworzono dla Pixel 5</string>
    <string name="tap_model_flame_name">147.1mm [5.8in] (Mały)</string>
    <string name="tap_model_flame_desc">Utworzono dla Pixel 4</string>
    <string name="tap_model_bramble_name">153.9mm [6.1in] (Średni)</string>
    <string name="tap_model_bramble_desc">Utworzono dla Pixel 4a 5G</string>
    <string name="tap_model_crosshatch_name">158mm [6.2in] (Duży)</string>
    <string name="tap_model_crosshatch_desc">Utworzono dla Pixel 3 XL</string>
    <string name="tap_model_coral_name">160.4mm [6.3in] (Duży)</string>
    <string name="tap_model_coral_desc">Utworzono dla Pixel 4 XL</string>

    <!-- Old (Android 11) models -->
    <string name="tap_model_pixel4_name">147.1mm [5.8in] (Mały)</string>
    <string name="tap_model_pixel4_desc">Utworzone dla Pixel 4</string>
    <string name="tap_model_pixel3xl_name">158mm [6.2in] (Średni)</string>
    <string name="tap_model_pixel3xl_desc">Utworzone dla Pixel 3 XL</string>
    <string name="tap_model_pixel4xl_name">160mm [6.3in] (Duży)</string>
    <string name="tap_model_pixel4xl_desc">Utworzone dla Pixel 4 XL</string>

    <!-- Samsung models -->
    <string name="tap_model_samsung_name">Samsung</string>
    <string name="tap_model_samsung_desc">Utworzone dla Samsung</string>

            <!-- Settings > Settings > Advanced -->
    <string name="setting_advanced">Advanced</string>
    <string name="setting_advanced_desc">Advanced settings and tweaks to change performance and more</string>
    <string name="setting_advanced_warning_desc">These settings are experimental and may not work on your device, or may cause Tap, Tap to stop working entirely.</string>
    <string name="setting_advanced_restart_service">Auto-restart service</string>
    <string name="setting_advanced_restart_service_desc">Attempt to automatically restart the Tap, Tap listener component once an hour.</string>
    <string name="setting_advanced_legacy_wake">Legacy Wake Device method</string>
    <string name="setting_advanced_legacy_wake_desc">Use the legacy method of waking the device with the \'Wake Device\' option enabled. This may not work on all devices, but may be more reliable in a few rare cases.</string>
    <string name="setting_advanced_tensor_low_power">Tensor Low Power Mode</string>
    <string name="setting_advanced_tensor_low_power_desc">Runs the Tensor model on the low power CPU if available; disable if you have performance issues or the gesture stops working entirely.</string>
    <string name="settings_advanced_monet_color_picker">Wallpaper Colour</string>
    <string name="settings_advanced_monet_color_picker_desc">Choose the colour from your wallpaper to use throughout Tap, Tap\'s UI</string>
    <string name="setting_advanced_custom_sensitivity">Custom sensitivity</string>
    <string name="setting_advanced_custom_sensitivity_desc">Set a custom sensitivity value for the gesture.\nImportant: Only use this if <b>none</b> of the built in sensitivity values are working for you</string>
    <string name="bs_advanced_custom_sensitivity">Custom Sensitivity</string>
    <string name="bs_advanced_custom_sensitivity_hint">Sensitivity</string>
    <string name="bs_advanced_custom_sensitivity_invalid">Invalid sensitivity</string>
    <string name="bs_advanced_custom_sensitivity_reset">Reset</string>

            <!-- Monet Color Picker -->
    <string name="color_picker_unavailable">Wallpaper Color Picker unavailable for the currently selected wallpaper</string>

            <!-- Settings > More -->
    <string name="settings_backup_restore">Backup &amp; Restore</string>
    <string name="settings_backup_restore_desc">Backup your settings to your device or the cloud</string>
    <string name="settings_backup_restore_backup">Backup</string>
    <string name="settings_backup_restore_backup_desc">Backup your settings to your device or the cloud</string>
    <string name="settings_backup_restore_restore">Restore</string>
    <string name="settings_backup_restore_restore_desc">Restore your settings from your device or the cloud</string>
    <string name="setting_internet">Allow Internet Access</string>
    <string name="setting_internet_desc">This will only be used to retrieve device specifications and to check for updates</string>
    <string name="setting_crash_reporting">Crash Notifications</string>
    <string name="setting_crash_reporting_desc">Show a notification if Tap, Tap crashes, allowing saving of a log to report on GitHub or XDA. This option <b>does not</b> automatically send crash data to a server.</string>
    <string name="battery_and_optimisation">Battery &amp; Optimisation</string>
    <string name="battery_and_optimisation_desc">Info on why Tap, Tap uses battery, and why it may be killed by your device when run in the background (and how to fix that)</string>
    <string name="xda_thread">XDA Thread</string>
    <string name="github">GitHub</string>
    <string name="libraries">Third party libraries</string>
    <string name="donate">Donate</string>
    <string name="twitter">Follow me on Twitter</string>
    <string name="about_version">Version %1s\nCreated by Kieron Quinn</string>

            <!-- Settings > More > Battery Optimisation -->
    <string name="settings_battery_header"><![CDATA[Tap, Tap uses sensor data in the background, which can be CPU and battery intensive. On devices with a dedicated ML accelerator (such as those with a Qualcomm Hexagon Tensor Accelerator), you may see a smaller battery impact.<br><a href="https://kieronquinn.co.uk/redirect/TapTap/battery">Tap here for some battery saving tips</a>.]]></string>
    <string name="settings_battery_info"><![CDATA[Tap, Tap requires the Android battery optimisation be disabled for the app. This helps prevent it being killed in the background.<br><b>Note:</b> On some devices, you may also need to disable extra settings to prevent the app being killed. <a href="https://dontkillmyapp.com/">Tap here for more info</a>.]]></string>
    <string name="settings_battery_disable_optimisation">Disable Battery Optimisation</string>
    <string name="settings_battery_disable_optimisation_desc_enabled">Android Battery Optimisation for Tap, Tap is enabled</string>
    <string name="settings_battery_disable_optimisation_desc_disabled">Android Battery Optimisation for Tap, Tap is disabled</string>
    <string name="settings_battery_oem_info">Your device appears to have some OEM-specific battery optimisations. Tap, Tap is unable to automatically request to disable them, please check your settings to verify they are disabled.</string>
    <string name="settings_battery_oem_button">Open OEM battery settings</string>

            <!-- Settings > More > Backup & Restore > Backup -->
    <string name="settings_backuprestore_backup_title">Creating backup…</string>
    <string name="settings_backuprestore_backup_desc">This shouldn\'t take long</string>
    <string name="settings_backuprestore_backup_done_title">Backup created</string>
    <string name="settings_backuprestore_backup_done_desc">Saved to %1s</string>
    <string name="settings_backuprestore_backup_error_title">Error creating backup</string>
    <string name="settings_backuprestore_backup_error_desc">There was an error saving your backup: %1s</string>

            <!-- Settings > More > Backup & Restore > Restore -->
    <string name="settings_backuprestore_restore_title">Restoring backup…</string>
    <string name="settings_backuprestore_restore_desc">This shouldn\'t take long</string>
    <string name="settings_backuprestore_restore_done_title">Backup restored</string>
    <string name="settings_backuprestore_restore_done_desc">Restored from backup %1s</string>
    <string name="settings_backuprestore_restore_error_title">Error restoring backup</string>
    <string name="settings_backuprestore_restore_error_desc">There was an error restoring your backup</string>
    <string name="backup_restore_error_type_failed_create_file">Failed to create file</string>
    <string name="backup_restore_error_type_failed_write_file">Failed to write to file</string>
    <string name="backup_restore_error_type_failed_unknown">Unknown error</string>
    <string name="settings_backup_restore_restore_infobox">Some actions, gates or requirements require additional setup or are incompatible with your device, please check them before continuing.</string>
    <string name="settings_backup_restore_restore_header_actions">Actions</string>
    <string name="settings_backup_restore_restore_header_gates">Gates</string>
    <string name="settings_backup_restore_restore_header_when_gates">Action Requirements</string>
    <string name="settings_backup_restore_restore_item_chip_action">Action</string>
    <string name="settings_backup_restore_restore_item_chip_gate">Gate</string>
    <string name="settings_backup_restore_restore_item_chip_requirement">Requirement</string>
    <string name="settings_backup_restore_restore_item_setup">Setup</string>
    <string name="settings_backup_restore_restore_item_skip">Skip</string>

            <!-- Settings > More > Contributors -->
    <string name="about_contributors">Contributors</string>
    <string name="about_contributors_main">Models</string>
    <string name="about_contributors_main_content"><![CDATA[\'Columbus\' Model and base code created by Google, from Android 11 Developer Preview 1 and Android 12 (<a href="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0">Apache License 2.0</a>)<br>\'RegiStar\' model from Samsung\'s Good Lock RegiStar module]]></string>
    <string name="about_contributors_community">Community Contributions</string>
    <string name="about_contributors_community_content"><b>Tasker integration</b>: João Dias\n<b>Music control actions</b>: timfedo\n<b>MD2 UI and Chrome Custom Tabs</b>: Giorgio Cantoni\n<b>Power Dialog action</b>: Adrian Campos\n<b>DND feedback and Sound Profiles action</b>: Ashutosh Singh\n<b>Launch Search action</b>: arkon\n<b>Force Do not Disturb action:</b> Kylian Meulin\n<b>Touch on Screen action:</b> Mauri de Souza Meneguzzo</string>
    <string name="about_contributors_icons">Icons</string>
    <string name="about_contributors_icons_content"><![CDATA[Icons by <b><a href="https://material.io/resources/icons">Material Icons</a></b> (<a href="https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html">Apache Licence 2.0</a>)<br><b><a href="https://github.com/Templarian/MaterialDesign">Material Design Icons</a></b> (<a href="https://github.com/Templarian/MaterialDesign/blob/master/LICENSE">Pictogrammers Free Licence</a>)<br><b><a href="https://www.freepik.com/">Freepik</a></b> (<a href="https://www.flaticon.com/license/pack/197373">Flaticon Licence</a>)<br><b><a href="https://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/smartphone_2628265">Vitaly Gorbachev</a></b> (<a href="https://www.flaticon.com/license/icon/2628265">Flaticon Licence</a>)]]></string>
    <string name="about_translators">Translators</string>

            <!-- Language headings, add to values.xml too -->
    <string name="translators_chinese">Chinese (Simplified)</string>
    <string name="translators_russian">Russian</string>
    <string name="translators_portuguese_br">Brazilian Portuguese</string>
    <string name="translators_ukrainian">Ukrainian</string>
    <string name="translators_italian">Italian</string>
    <string name="translators_polish">Polish</string>
    <string name="translators_french">French</string>
    <string name="translators_spanish">Spanish</string>
    <string name="translators_vietnamese">Vietnamese</string>
    <string name="translators_german">German</string>
    <string name="translators_turkish">Turkish</string>
    <string name="translators_chinese_traditional">Chinese (Traditional)</string>

            <!-- Actions -->
    <string name="action_launch_camera">Launch camera</string>
    <string name="action_launch_camera_desc">Launch your default camera app. This action will be skipped if the camera is already running.</string>
    <string name="action_snapchat">Quick Tap to Snap</string>
    <string name="action_snapchat_desc">Launch Snapchat\'s Quick Tap to Snap feature, if available (this action may require some additional setup).</string>
    <string name="action_home">Home</string>
    <string name="action_home_desc">Simulate pressing the home button</string>
    <string name="action_back">Back</string>
    <string name="action_back_desc">Simulate pressing the back button</string>
    <string name="action_recents">Open recents</string>
    <string name="action_recents_desc">Open the recents by simulating pressing the recents button. On devices that support it, using this action when recents is already open will switch to the first backgrounded app</string>
    <string name="action_notifications">Open notifications</string>
    <string name="action_notifications_desc">Open the notification shade. On supported devices, this will close the notification shade if it\'s open.</string>
    <string name="action_quick_settings">Quick settings</string>
    <string name="action_quick_settings_desc">Open the quick settings shade. On supported devices, this will close the quick settings shade if it\'s open</string>
    <string name="action_screenshot">Screenshot</string>
    <string name="action_screenshot_desc">Take a screenshot using the system screenshot UI</string>
    <string name="action_lock_screen">Lock the screen</string>
    <string name="action_lock_screen_desc">Lock the screen by simulating the power button being pressed</string>
    <string name="action_power_dialog">Power Menu</string>
    <string name="action_power_dialog_desc">Opens the power dialog by simulating the power button being held</string>
    <string name="action_toggle_pause">Play/Pause</string>
    <string name="action_toggle_pause_desc">Play/Pause current playing audio</string>
    <string name="action_previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="action_previous_desc">Play previous audio</string>
    <string name="action_next">Next</string>
    <string name="action_next_desc">Play next audio</string>
    <string name="action_device_controls">Launch Device Controls</string>
    <string name="action_device_controls_desc">Show the Device (Home) controls, as if the Quick Settings tile has been clicked</string>
    <string name="action_quick_access_wallet">Launch Quick Access Wallet</string>
    <string name="action_quick_access_wallet_desc">Show the Quick Access Wallet, as if the Quick Settings tile has been clicked</string>
    <string name="action_click_quick_setting">Click Quick Setting</string>
    <string name="action_click_quick_setting_desc">Simulate clicking a Quick Setting tile</string>
    <string name="action_click_quick_setting_desc_formatted">Simulate clicking %1s (Quick Setting tile)</string>
    <string name="action_flashlight">Flashlight</string>
    <string name="action_flashlight_desc">Toggle the flashlight. This action will fail if the camera is in use by another app.</string>
    <string name="action_launch_app">Launch app</string>
    <string name="action_launch_app_desc">Launch an app</string>
    <string name="action_launch_app_desc_formattable">Launch %1s. This action will be skipped if it is already running.</string>
    <string name="action_launch_assistant">Launch Assistant</string>
    <string name="action_launch_assistant_desc">Launch your default assistant app</string>
    <string name="action_launch_search">Launch search</string>
    <string name="action_launch_search_desc">Start a Google Search</string>
    <string name="action_tasker_event">Tasker Event</string>
    <string name="action_tasker_event_desc">Trigger the Tasker Event plugin</string>
    <string name="action_tasker_task">Tasker Task</string>
    <string name="action_tasker_task_desc">Run a specified Tasker task</string>
    <string name="action_tasker_task_desc_formatted">Run a Tasker task (%1s)</string>
    <string name="action_volume_panel">Show volume panel</string>
    <string name="action_volume_panel_desc">Show the system volume panel with the sound stream for adjustment showing</string>
    <string name="action_volume_up">Volume up</string>
    <string name="action_volume_up_desc">Increase the volume of the current sound stream</string>
    <string name="action_volume_down">Volume down</string>
    <string name="action_volume_down_desc">Decrease the volume of the current sound stream</string>
    <string name="action_volume_toggle_mute">Toggle mute</string>
    <string name="action_volume_toggle_mute_desc">Turn mute on/off for the current sound stream</string>
    <string name="action_wake_device">Wake device</string>
    <string name="action_wake_device_desc">Wake the device up if the screen is off. This overrides the setting in the feedback settings, is skipped if the display is on, and will not work if you have the \"Display off\" gate enabled</string>
    <string name="actions_sound_profile">Switch sound profiles</string>
    <string name="actions_sound_profile_desc">Switch between sound profiles of your device: Vibrate/Silent/Loud</string>
    <string name="do_not_disturb">Toggle do not disturb profile</string>
    <string name="do_not_disturb_desc">Force sound profile of your device: Silent</string>
    <string name="action_launch_shortcut">Launch a shortcut</string>
    <string name="action_launch_shortcut_desc">Launch a shortcut such as Google Maps directions</string>
    <string name="action_launch_shortcut_desc_formattable">Launch %1s (shortcut into the app)</string>
    <string name="action_launch_shortcut_toast">This shortcut is currently not supported</string>
    <string name="action_launch_app_shortcut">Launch App Shortcut</string>
    <string name="action_launch_app_shortcut_desc">Launch an App Shortcut, usually a deep link into an app such as a chat conversation</string>
    <string name="action_launch_app_shortcut_desc_formattable">Launch %1s (app shortcut into the app)</string>
    <string name="action_split_screen">Split screen</string>
    <string name="action_split_screen_desc">Start or stop split screen mode with the current app (does not work when on the homescreen)</string>
    <string name="action_reachability">Launch reachability</string>
    <string name="action_reachability_desc">Experimental: Launch a reachbility-esque mode using split screen, with an empty top half of the screen and the current app on the bottom. Note: You may be required to reopen the current app when starting and ending this mode</string>
    <string name="action_camera_shutter">Camera Button</string>
    <string name="action_camera_shutter_desc">Simulate a camera button press, taking a photo if the camera is open (supported camera apps only)</string>
    <string name="action_google_voice_access">Trigger Google Voice Access</string>
    <string name="action_google_voice_access_desc">Triggers the Google Voice Access <b>accessibility app</b>, if it is running (this is NOT assistant or voice search)</string>
    <string name="action_hamburger">Hamburger Menu / Back</string>
    <string name="action_hamburger_desc">This action presses the screen at the position the hamburger menu usually is.\n<b>Important warning</b>: This will tap <b>anything</b> at the position where the menu usually is (top left), so will also sometimes go back, and may even tap other elements on the screen in that position, including other buttons. <b>Use with extreme caution</b>, consider using triple tap and app requirements to limit it.</string>
    <string name="action_accessibility_button">Trigger Accessibility Button</string>
    <string name="action_accessibility_button_desc">Simulate the accessibility button, which can be used to trigger other services such as Select to Speak</string>
    <string name="action_accessibility_button_chooser">Accessibility Button Chooser</string>
    <string name="action_accessibility_button_chooser_desc">Bring up the Accessibility Button\'s chooser menu</string>
    <string name="action_accessibility_shortcut">Trigger Accessibility Shortcut</string>
    <string name="action_accessibility_shortcut_desc">Trigger the Accessibility Shortcut. Make sure Tap, Tap is not set to use the shortcut before using this action!</string>
    <string name="action_app_drawer">App Drawer</string>
    <string name="action_app_drawer_desc">Open the app drawer of a <b>supported launcher</b>. This only works on launchers based on Android 11.</string>
    <string name="action_accept_call">Accept Call</string>
    <string name="action_accept_call_desc">Accept call if there is one ringing</string>
    <string name="action_reject_call">Reject Call</string>
    <string name="action_reject_call_desc">Reject call if there is one ringing, or hang up if there is one ongoing</string>
    <string name="action_swipe_up">Swipe Up</string>
    <string name="action_swipe_up_desc">Perform a swipe up gesture on the current app</string>
    <string name="action_swipe_down">Swipe Down</string>
    <string name="action_swipe_down_desc">Perform a swipe down gesture on the current app</string>
    <string name="action_swipe_left">Swipe Left</string>
    <string name="action_swipe_left_desc">Perform a swipe left gesture on the current app</string>
    <string name="action_swipe_right">Swipe Right</string>
    <string name="action_swipe_right_desc">Perform a swipe right gesture on the current app</string>
    <string name="action_selector_unavailable">Sorry, this action is not compatible with your device (%1s).</string>
    <string name="action_alt_tab">Switch to last app</string>
    <string name="action_alt_tab_desc">Switch to the most recent app by simulating double tapping the recents button (supported devices only)</string>
    <string name="action_alarm_timer">Dismiss Alarm / Timer</string>
    <string name="action_alarm_snooze">Snooze Alarm</string>
    <string name="action_alarm_timer_desc">Dismisses an alarm or timer, if there is one going off (supported Clock apps only)</string>
    <string name="action_alarm_snooze_desc">Snoozes an alarm, if there is one going off (supported Clock apps only)</string>
    <string name="action_touch">Touch on screen</string>
    <string name="action_touch_desc">This action presses the screen at a random point to generate a touch gesture.</string>
    <string name="action_force_rotate">Rotate</string>
    <string name="action_force_rotate_desc">Simulate rotating the device to landscape or portrait, if the app supports it.\n<b>Note:</b> This disables auto rotate when used.</string>

    <string name="action_unsupported_reason_min_sdk">Incompatible with your version of Android</string>
    <string name="action_unsupported_reason_tasker">Tasker is required</string>
    <string name="action_unsupported_reason_snapchat">Snapchat is required</string>

    <!-- Gates -->
    <string name="gate_charging_state">Ładowanie</string>
    <string name="gate_charging_state_desc_a">Blokuj gest, gdy urządzenie się ładuje</string>
    <string name="gate_charging_state_desc_when_a">Wykonaj raz, gdy urządzenie zostało podłączone do ładowarki</string>
    <string name="gate_telephony_activity">Podczas połączenia</string>
    <string name="gate_telephony_activity_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy urządzienie jest w trakcie połączenia. Obsługiwane są zwykłe połączenia - nie VoIP, np. WhatsApp</string>
    <string name="gate_telephony_activity_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy urządzenie jest w trakcie połączenia</string>
    <string name="gate_usb_state">Urządzenie USB</string>
    <string name="gate_usb_state_desc_a">Blokuj gest, gdy urządzenie USB, taki jak pendrive jest podłączone</string>
    <string name="gate_usb_state_desc_when_a">Wykonaj raz, gdy urządzenie USB jest podłączone</string>
    <string name="gate_camera_visibility">Aparat</string>
    <string name="gate_camera_visibility_desc">Blokuje gest po otwarciu dowolnej aplikacji aparatu. Uwaga: Może spowodować problem z akcją Uruchom aparat.</string>
    <string name="gate_camera_visibility_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy aplikacja aparatu jest otwarta</string>
    <string name="gate_power_state">Ekran wyłączony</string>
    <string name="gate_power_state_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy ekran urządzenia jest wyłączony</string>
    <string name="gate_power_state_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy ekran urządzenia jest wyłączony</string>
    <string name="gate_power_state_inverse">Ekran włączony</string>
    <string name="gate_power_state_inverse_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy ekran urządzenia jest włączony</string>
    <string name="gate_power_state_inverse_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy ekran urządzenia jest włączony</string>
    <string name="gate_app_showing">Wyświetlana aplikacja</string>
    <string name="gate_app_showing_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy określona aplikacja jest wyświetlana na ekranie</string>
    <string name="gate_app_showing_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy określona aplikacja jest wyświetlana na ekranie</string>
    <string name="gate_app_showing_desc_when_formatted">Wykonaj raz, gdy %1s jest wyświetlana na ekranie</string>
    <string name="gate_app_showing_desc_formatted">Blokuje gest, gdy %1s jest wyświetlana na ekranie</string>
    <string name="gate_keyboard_visibility">Widoczna Klawiatura</string>
    <string name="gate_keyboard_visibility_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy klawiatura jest widoczna i używana. Może nie zadziałać w momencie, gdy nie piszesz na klawiaturze.</string>
    <string name="gate_keyboard_visibility_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy klawiatura jest widoczna i używana. Może nie zadziałać w momencie, gdy nie piszesz na klawiaturze.</string>
    <string name="gate_orientation_landscape">Orientacja pozioma</string>
    <string name="gate_orientation_landscape_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy telefon jest w orientacji poziomej</string>
    <string name="gate_orientation_landscape_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy urządzenie jest w orientacji poziomej</string>
    <string name="gate_orientation_portrait">Orientacja pionowa</string>
    <string name="gate_orientation_portrait_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy urządzenie jest w orientacji pionowej</string>
    <string name="gate_orientation_portrait_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy urządzenie jest w orientacji pionowej</string>
    <string name="gate_table">Stolik</string>
    <string name="gate_table_desc">Blokuj gest, gdy telefon leży na płaskiej powierzchni, np stole</string>
    <string name="gate_table_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy telefon leży na płaskiej powierzchni, np stole</string>
    <string name="gate_pocket">Kieszeń</string>
    <string name="gate_pocket_desc">Blokuj gest, gdy czujnik zbliżeniowy wykryje obiekt. Ta blokada zadziała, gdy telefon włożysz do kieszeni lub położysz ekranem do dołu na stole</string>
    <string name="gate_pocket_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy czujnik zbliżeniowy wykryje obiekt. Akcja wykona się, gdy telefon włożysz do kieszeni lub położysz ekranem do dołu na stole</string>
    <string name="gate_headset_inverse">Brak Słuchawek</string>
    <string name="gate_headset_desc_inverse">Blokuje gest, gdy żadne słuchawki przewodowe i bezprzewodowe nie są podłączone</string>
    <string name="gate_headset_desc_when_inverse">Wykonaj raz, gdy żadne słuchawki przewodowe i bezprzewodowe nie są podłączone</string>
    <string name="gate_headset">Słuchawki</string>
    <string name="gate_headset_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy słuchawki przewodowe lub bezprzewodowe są podłączone</string>
    <string name="gate_headset_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy słuchawki przewodowe lub bezprzewodowe są podłączone</string>
    <string name="gate_music">Muzyka Gra</string>
    <string name="gate_music_inverse">Muzka Nie Gra</string>
    <string name="gate_music_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy muzyka jest odtwarzana</string>
    <string name="gate_music_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy muzyka jest odtwarzana</string>
    <string name="gate_music_desc_when_inverse">Wykonaj raz, gdy muzyka nie jest odtwarzana</string>
    <string name="gate_music_desc_inverse">Blokuje gest, gdy muzyka nie jest odtwarzana</string>
    <string name="gate_lock_screen_showing">Widoczna Blokada Ekranu</string>
    <string name="gate_lock_screen_showing_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy widoczna jest blokada ekranu</string>
    <string name="gate_lock_screen_showing_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy widoczna jest blokada ekranu</string>
    <string name="gate_lock_screen_showing_inverse">Brak Blokady Ekranu</string>
    <string name="gate_lock_screen_showing_inverse_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy blokada ekranu nie jest widoczna</string>
    <string name="gate_lock_screen_showing_inverse_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy blokada ekranu nie jest widoczna</string>
    <string name="gate_alarm">Alarm / Minutnik</string>
    <string name="gate_alarm_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy alarm lub minutnik są aktywne</string>
    <string name="gate_alarm_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy alarm lub minutnik są aktywne</string>
    <string name="gate_foldable_closed">Składane: Telefon Zlożony</string>
    <string name="gate_foldable_closed_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy urządzenie jest złożone / zamknięte</string>
    <string name="gate_foldable_closed_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy urządzenie jest złożone / zamknięte</string>
    <string name="gate_foldable_open">Składane: Telefon Rozłożony</string>
    <string name="gate_foldable_open_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy urządzenie jest rozłożóne / otwarte</string>
    <string name="gate_foldable_open_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy urządzenie jest rozłożone / otwarte</string>
    <string name="gate_low_battery">Niski Poziom Baterii</string>
    <string name="gate_low_battery_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy poziom baterii jest poniżej 15%</string>
    <string name="gate_low_battery_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy poziom baterii jest poniżej 15%</string>
    <string name="gate_battery_saver">Oszczędzanie Baterii</string>
    <string name="gate_battery_saver_desc">Blokuje gest, gdy funkcja Oszczędzania Baterii jest włączona</string>
    <string name="gate_battery_saver_desc_when">Wykonaj raz, gdy funkcja Oszczędzania Baterii jest włączona</string>

    <string name="gate_unsupported_reason_min_sdk">Niekompatybilne z Twoją wersją Android</string>
    <string name="gate_unsupported_reason_foldable">Wymaga kompatybilnego składanego telefonu</string>

            <!-- Notification channels & content -->
    <string name="tap_notification_title">Tap, Tap Service</string>
    <string name="tap_notification_content">Tap, Tap is running in the background. Tap to hide.</string>
    <string name="tap_notification_channel_title">Background notification</string>
    <string name="tap_notification_channel_description">Notification used to keep Tap, Tap running in the background when the option to use a separate service is enabled</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_actions_title">Actions</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_actions_content">Notifications about actions, including errors while running them</string>
    <string name="notification_action_flashlight_error_title">Error Toggling Flashlight</string>
    <string name="notification_action_flashlight_error_content">Camera permission required, tap to open settings.</string>
    <string name="notification_action_overlay_error_title">Draw Over Other Apps Permission Required</string>
    <string name="notification_action_overlay_error_content">This action requires the Draw Over Other apps permission, due to system limitations. Tap to grant permission.</string>
    <string name="notification_action_accessibility_error_title">Accessibility Service Not Enabled</string>
    <string name="notification_action_accessibility_error_content">This action requires the Accessibility Service, tap to enable. If you are seeing this when it is enabled, disable and re-enable the service.</string>
    <string name="notification_gate_accessibility_error_content">This gate requires the Accessibility Service, tap to enable. If you are seeing this when it is enabled, disable and re-enable the service.</string>
    <string name="notification_action_gesture_accessibility_error_title">Gesture Accessibility Service Not Enabled</string>
    <string name="notification_action_gesture_accessibility_error_content">This action requires the Gesture Accessibility Service, tap to enable. If you are seeing this when it is enabled, disable and re-enable the service.</string>
    <string name="notification_action_system_settings_error_title">Write Settings Permission Required</string>
    <string name="notification_action_system_settings_error_content">This action requires the Write Settings permission, tap to grant</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_service_title">Service</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_service_content">Notifications about the service, including loading and errors</string>
    <string name="notification_service_loading_title">Starting Service…</string>
    <string name="notification_service_loading_title_restart">Restarting Service…</string>
    <string name="notification_service_loading_content">Tap, Tap service is loading</string>
    <string name="notification_service_error_title">Error Starting Service</string>
    <string name="notification_service_running_error_title">Error Reconnecting to Shizuku Service</string>
    <string name="notification_service_error_content_shizuku_not_running">Unable to connect to Shizuku, please make sure it is running and then retry.</string>
    <string name="notification_service_error_content_shizuku_permission_denied">Permission denied when connecting to Shizuku, please grant Tap, Tap permission in Shizuku and then retry.</string>
    <string name="notification_service_error_action_retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="notification_service_error_root_title">Error Connecting to Service</string>
    <string name="notification_service_error_root_content">Make sure you have granted root access to Tap, Tap</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_crash_title">Crashes</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_crash_content">Notifications when Tap, Tap crashes to save errors</string>
    <string name="notification_crash_title">Tap, Tap has crashed!</string>
    <string name="notification_crash_content">Tap to view the crash details and export a log to be sent on GitHub or XDA. You can disable crash notifications in Tap, Tap\'s settings.</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_native_setup_title">Native Mode Setup</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_native_setup_content">Notifications showing instructions during setting up Native Mode</string>
    <string name="notification_native_setup_title">Finish setting up Native Mode</string>
    <string name="notification_native_setup_content">Set the action to Open App > Tap, Tap to finish setting up Native Mode</string>
    <string name="tap_update_notification_channel_title">Update notifications</string>
    <string name="tap_update_notification_channel_description">Notifications shown when the app checks for updates once a day</string>
    <string name="tap_update_notification_title">Tap, Tap update available</string>
    <string name="tap_update_notification_content">An update is available for Tap, Tap (%1s to %1s)</string>

            <!-- Shared Pickers, for Gates & Actions -->
    <string name="settings_shared_app_shortcuts_selector_loading">Ładowanie Skrótów Aplikacji…</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_shortcuts_selector_loading">Ładowanie Skrótów…</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_shortcuts_selector_error">Nie mogę załadować skrótów aplikacji, spróbuj ponownie. Jeżeli problem się powtarza, zrestartuj Shizuku używając ADB.</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_shizuku_permission_flow_toolbar_title">Shizuku / Sui</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_shizuku_permission_flow_title">Sprawdzanie dostępności Shizuku / Sui</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_shizuku_permission_flow_content">Proces ten może zająć do 10 sekund</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_shizuku_permission_flow_error_title">Nie znaleziono Shizuku / Sui</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_shizuku_permission_flow_error_content">Shizuku lub Sui nie zostały odnalezione na Twoim urządzeniu. Musisz zainstalować jedną z tych aplikacji aby użyć %s.\n\n<b>Uwaga:</b> Jeżeli masz już Shizuku lub Sui, upewnij się że działają oraz, że nie odmówiłeś wymaganych uprawnień.</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_shizuku_permission_flow_error_content_action">akcja</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_shizuku_permission_flow_error_content_gate">brama</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_shizuku_permission_flow_error_card_shizuku_title">Shizuku</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_shizuku_permission_flow_error_card_shizuku_content">Shizuku is a non-root app that allows apps like Tap, Tap to run code with special permissions. It does this by running a command on ADB (Android Debug Bridge) Shell, once per reboot. On Android 11+ devices, this can be done without a computer, but on older versions you will need to connect to a computer once per reboot to restart Shizuku.</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_shizuku_permission_flow_error_card_shizuku_button">Pobierz Shizuku</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_shizuku_permission_flow_error_card_sui_content">Sui is a Magisk module that allows apps like Tap, Tap to run code as root. It uses the same framework as Shizuku, and therefore works with Shizuku apps, but does not require manual starting after reboots, this is done automatically.\n<b>If you are not sure what root or Magisk is, use Shizuku instead.</b></string>
    <string name="settings_shared_shizuku_permission_flow_error_card_sui_title">Sui</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_shizuku_permission_flow_error_card_sui_button">Pobierz Sui</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_package_selector_loading">Ładowanie Aplikacji…</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_package_selector_empty">Nie odnaleziono Aplikacji</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_snapchat_loading_title">Sprawdzanie dostępności…</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_snapchat_loading_content">Przyznaj uprawnienia root jeżeli wymagane</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_snapchat_setup_root_title">Wymagana dodatkowa konfiguracja</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_snapchat_setup_root_content">To enable Quick Tap to Snap on your device, please follow these steps:\n<b>You must be signed into Snapchat for this to work</b>\n1.) Disable your internet connection - both WiFi and mobile data (use Airplane Mode ideally). <b>Do not re-enable it until you have completed these steps.</b>\n2.) Select the option below to open Snapchat - you must use this button as it has to open with certain options to show the prompt.\n3.) Snapchat will open and prompt you to unlock to complete setting up - this is normal, simply OK the dialog.\n4.) A dialog will appear asking you to enable Quick Tap to Snap, enable it. <b>You will not see a system prompt to enable it, this is normal.</b>\n5.) Return to Tap, Tap by closing Snapchat to complete setup.</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_snapchat_setup_root_button">Otwórz Snapchat</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_snapchat_setup_no_root_title">Wymagana dodatkowa konfiguracja</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_snapchat_setup_no_root_content">To setup Quick Tap to Snap, there are a few steps to follow. These steps require rebooting your phone and re-activating the system Quick Tap gesture temporarily (which will prevent access to Tap, Tap until the steps are finished), so they have been put on an external site to make them more accessible.</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_snapchat_setup_no_root_button">Otwórz instrukcje</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_snapchat_setup_incompatible_title">Niekompatybilne</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_snapchat_setup_incompatible_content">Sorry, Quick Tap to Snap requires root access to be enabled on your device.</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_snapchat_setup_incompatible_button">Zamknij</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_snapchat_setup_error">Problem z dostępnością, spróbuj ponownie</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_snapchat_setup_error_network">Najpierw wyłącz WiFi oraz dane mobilne</string>
    <string name="item_settings_shared_quick_settings_header_content">Due to system limitations, there are some restrictions:\n- Quick Settings tiles\' titles cannot be retrieved, so please refer to your notification shade to match against the order.\n- Only custom tiles can be clicked, not the stock ones such as Internet\n- On some devices, the tile must be on page 1 or 2 of your quick settings for the click to work.</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_quick_settings_empty">Nie odnaleziono kafelka szybkich ustawień</string>
    <string name="settings_shared_quick_settings_loading">Ładowanie kafelków szybkich ustawień…</string>

    <!-- No root bottom sheet -->
    <string name="bs_no_root_title">Brak uprawnień root</string>
    <string name="bs_no_root_content">Uprawnienia root nie zostały odnalezione lub nie zostały przyznane. Uprawnienia root muszą być aktywne, aby użyć tej akcji.</string>

    <!-- Permission Toasts (shown when launching external apps) -->
    <string name="call_phone_permission_toast">Musisz przyznać uprawnienia \"Telefon\" dla Tap, Tap, aby użyć akcji skrót. Uprawnienia te możesz nadać w ustawieniach swojego telefonu.</string>
    <string name="permission_toast">Nadaj uprawnienia %1s w ustawieniach, aby kontunuować.</string>
    <string name="permission_toast_draw_over_apps">Przyznaj Tap, Tap uprawnienia do wyświetlania nad innymi aplikacjami</string>
    <string name="tasker_content_toast">Włącz opcję \"Allow External Access\" w ustaawieniach Tasker.</string>

    <!-- Update downloader -->
    <string name="snackbar_update">Dostępna aktualizacja</string>
    <string name="snackbar_update_button">Aktualizuj</string>
    <string name="settings_update_heading">Wersja Tap, Tap %1s</string>
    <string name="settings_update_subheading">Aktualna wersja %1s</string>
    <string name="settings_update_changes">Zmiany</string>
    <string name="settings_update_open_installer"Rozpocznij instalację</string>
    <string name="settings_update_done">Pobieranie ukończone</string>
    <string name="settings_update_loading">Ładowanie…</string>
    <string name="settings_update_fab">Pobierz</string>
    <string name="download_manager_description">Pobieranie aktualizacji…</string>
    <string name="update_downloader_downloading_title">Pobieranie aktualizacji…</string>
    <string name="update_downloader_downloading_failed">Pobieranie nie powiodło się</string>
    <string name="update_downloader_github">Pobierz przez przeglądarkę</string>

    <!-- Reachability UI -->
    <string name="reachability_left_handed_info">Naciśnij i przytrzymaj ikonę powiadomienia, aby zmienić jej pozycję</string>
    
    <!-- Quick Settings Tile subtitles -->
    <string name="qs_subtitle_running">Działa</string>
    <string name="qs_subtitle_disabled">Wyłączony</string>
    <string name="qs_subtitle_not_running">Nie działa</string>

    <!-- Tasker descriptions & labels -->
    <string name="tasker_description_triple">Zadziała, gdy stukniesz trzy razy w tył telefonu</string>
    <string name="tasker_description_double">Zadziała, gdy stukniesz dwa razy w tył telefonu</string>
    <string name="tasker_config_label">Podwójne stuknięcie</string>
    <string name="tasker_config_label_triple">Potrójne stuknięcie</string>

    <!-- Accessibility Service info in settings -->
    <string name="accessibility_service_label">Tap, Tap</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_label_gesture">Usługa pomocnicza Tap, Tap</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_description">Usługa ułatwień dostępu Tap, Tap\n\n<b>Ważna Informacja: Żadne dane z Twoich aplikacji nie są zbierane. Ta usługa służy wyłącznie do utrzymania aktywności aplikacji Tap, Tap i umożliwia interakcję z urządzeniem</b></string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_description_gesture">Usługa ułatwień dostępu gestów Tap, Tap. \n\n<b>Nie musisz włączać tej usługi jeżeli aplikacja Cię o to nie poprosi. Usługa ta jest wymagana przez niektóre akcje.</b>\n\n<b>Ważna informacja: Żadne dane z Twoich aplikacji nie są zbierane. Ta usługa służy wyłącznie do zapewnienia interakcji gestów z urządzeniem.\n\nJest to osobna usługa związana z tym architekturą systemu Android i z tym jak aplikacje dostosowują swój interfejs użytkownika, gdy włączone są usługi umożliwiające wykonywanie gestów.</b></string>

    <!-- Crash Reporting -->
    <string name="crash_reporting_title">Tap, Tap uległ awarii</string>
    <string name="crash_reporting_save">Zapisz raport</string>
    <string name="crash_reporting_content_intro"><![CDATA[Tap, Tap uległ awarii. Proszę zgłoś problem, uwzględniając dostępny report na stronie <a href="https://kieronquinn.co.uk/redirect/TapTap/github">GitHub</a> lub <a href="https://kieronquinn.co.uk/redirect/TapTap/xda">XDA</a>. Jeżeli bład wystąpił podczas wykonywania gestu, akcji lub blokady, proszę załączyć zrzut ekranu przedstawiający Twoją konfigurację.<br><br><b>Ważne: Zanim zgłosisz problem, upewnij się, że nie został on już zgłoszony wcześniej.</b><br><br>Raport jest również widoczny poniżej.]]></string>
    <string name="crash_reporting_toast_success">Raport zapisany</string>
    <string name="crash_reporting_toast_failed">Bład zapisu raportu</string>


</resources>
